[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Grizzly bears hibernate through the winter.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nickname of burglars Marv and Harry in the movie Home Alone?", "correct_answer": "The Wet Bandits", "incorrect_answers": ["Barney  Clyde", "Rob  Stealin", "The James Gang"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Microbes are generally considered to be this.", "correct_answer": "Both harmless and deadly.", "incorrect_answers": ["Harmless", "Illness-causing", "Deadly"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Monopoly, one of the best-selling commercial board games in the world named after the well-know economic term, the course of the game is determined mainly by which two of these factors?", "correct_answer": "Chance and decision-making", "incorrect_answers": ["Logic and chance", "Skill and concentration", "Decision-making and strategy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character in the comedy film The Benchwarmers works as a video store clerk?", "correct_answer": "Ritchie", "incorrect_answers": ["Gus", "Clark", "no one"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these ships does Luke Skywalker fly?", "correct_answer": "X-wing", "incorrect_answers": ["Y-Wing", "Bomber", "V-Wing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jane Porter is the love interest of this fictional character.", "correct_answer": "Tarzan", "incorrect_answers": ["Batman", "Superman", "Spiderman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following medications treats depression?", "correct_answer": "Zoloft (sertraline)", "incorrect_answers": ["Augmentin (amoxicillin/clavulanic acid)", "Benadryl (diphenhydramine)", "Darvon (propoxyphene)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Identical twins have identical fingerprints.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is NOT a constellation of the Zodiac (the ring of constellations that the sun passes through each year)?", "correct_answer": "The Winged Horse", "incorrect_answers": ["The Fish", "The Crab", "The Archer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the name of a Danish delicacy?", "correct_answer": "Yule Brod", "incorrect_answers": ["Retsina", "Marmite", "Schmaltz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By what name did Marco Polo call the capital of China, present-day Beijing?", "correct_answer": "Cambaluc", "incorrect_answers": ["Canton", "Peijing", "Nahnjing"]}]